If you have AT&T, your network said, not today, last week, last Thursday morning, your phone said, nope.
Now, by little after 3 p.m., roughly 11 hours after reports of the outage first emerged,
AT&T said that they had restored service to all impacted customers.
The comedy is that they told you that potentially impacted customers, they're going to compensate y'all.
They got you.
They're going to give you $5.
They're going to give you $5 for your troubles.
I say, you know what?
This is rough.
But let's think of some silver linings for your phone being without self-service for 11 to 12 hours.
Maybe you missed all the debt collectors calling you, okay?
Maybe this was a day you got a break from them saying, hey, where's our money?
Maybe you didn't have to agree about getting a call from a baby mom or a baby dad.
Maybe, if you are students out there, you could have lucked out on teachers calling your parents to report your bad behavior.
Okay.
That's always positive.
If you acted up that day, if you acted up that day, there was no way for them to call before you got home.
Look at you.
And finally, a day went by where you did not have to hear about your car's extended warranty.
That's the one.
That's the one right there.
Do you have AT&T?
What was it like for you?
Call me up.
1-855-AMAND-8.
That's 1-855-262-6328.
We are, we are, we are.